mypopkorn.com 2011-12-31

# myPOPKORN.com – Never miss a thing

Last Revised on: 26/March/2008

Digital Media Convergence Limited ("myPOPKORN.com ") respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy provides the manner your data is collected and used by myPOPKORN.com. You are advised to please read the Privacy Policy carefully. By accessing the services provided by myPOPKORN.com you agree to the collection and use of your data by MyPopkorn.com in the manner provided in this Privacy Policy. 

**We want you to :**

* feel comfortable using our web site
* feel secure submitting information to us 
* contact us with your questions or concerns about privacy on this site 
* know that by using our site you are consenting to the collection of your data

 **WHAT INFORMATION IS, OR MAY BE, COLLECTED FROM YOU?**  
We will automatically receive and collect certain anonymous information in standard usage logs through our Web server, including computer-identification information obtained from "cookies", sent to your browser from: 

* web server cookie stored on your hard drive 
* an IP address, assigned to the computer which you use
* the type of computer you're using
* the type of web browser you're using 

We may collect the following personally identifiable information about you:  

* name including first and last name
* alternate email address
* mobile phone number and contact details
* ZIP/Postal code
* demographic profile (like your age, gender, occupation, education, address and durables owned);
* preferences and interests (such as news, sports, travel and so on);
* opinions of features on our website.

We may also collect the following information:  

* about the pages you visit/access
* the links you click on our site
* the number of times you access the page. You can terminate your account at any time. However, your information may remain stored in archive on our servers even after the deletion or the termination of your account. 

1\. **User provided information:** We may collect and store information, personal or otherwise, that you voluntarily supply either while on the Site or in responding via email in connection with a feature provided on the Site. Some examples of this type of information include demographic information that you electronically submit when you sign up for access to certain features on the Site, information (such as your name or email address) that you electronically submit when you register for surveys or contests on the Site, information that you post on message boards on the Site, and information contained in search requests or questions that you submit to the Site. If you decline to supply or provide us with certain information while using the Site, you may not be able to use or participate in some or all of the features offered through the Site.

2. **Cookies information:** When you visit the MYPOPKORN Site, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. MYPOPKORN uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the MYPOPKORN Site may not function properly.   
In addition, third party advertisers or third party ad servers that place and present advertising on the Site also may collect information from you via cookies, web beacons, clear .gifs or similar technologies. These third party advertisers and ad servers may use the information they collect to help present their advertisements, to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness, or for other uses. The use and collection of your information by these third party advertisers and ad servers is governed by the relevant third party's privacy policy and is not covered by our privacy policy. Indeed, the privacy policy of these third party advertisers and ad servers may be different from our privacy policy.

3\. **Log file information:** When you use the MYPOPKORN Site, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

4. **Clear / transparent GIFs information:** When you use the MYPOPKORN Site, we may employ "clear GIFs" (a.k.a. Web Beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our users / members anonymously. In addition, we may also use clear GIFs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients.

 **HOW IS THIS INFORMATION USED?**

1\. If you submit personally identifiable information to us through the MYPOPKORN Site, then we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the MYPOPKORN Site.

2\. Any personal information that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, within your public profile page, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected, seen and used by others besides us. We cannot be and are not responsible for any unauthorized third party use of such information. Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other users / members when you send messages through the MYPOPKORN Site and other users / members can contact you through messages and comments. 

3\. We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may provide our advertisers with information about you and other visitors that will enable our advertisers to better target ads to specific types of visitors. We reserve the right to use and to disclose to third parties all of the information that we collect online about you and other visitors in any way and for any purpose, with one important exception viz. We will not use the information that we collect online from you while you are using the Site, nor will we authorize third parties to use such information, to mail or email promotional offers directly to you unless you have specifically informed us that you would like to receive promotional offers from us and/or from third parties. If you choose to receive these promotional offers, then your information may be used for direct mail or email marketing. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major MYPOPKORN Site changes or for customer service purposes).

4\. We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous user usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the MYPOPKORN Site and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing user / member preferences and trends.

5\. We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the MYPOPKORN Site; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, and contests.

6\. The Site includes links to other websites and provides access to products and services offered by third parties, whose privacy policies we do not control. When you access another website or purchase third party products or services through the Site, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting or the provider of such products or services.

7\. We may also make some content, products and services available through our Site through cooperative relationships with third party providers, where the brands of our provider partner appear on the Site in connection with such content, products and/or services. We may share with our provider partner any information you provide, or that is collected, in the course of visiting any pages that are made available in cooperation with our provider partner. In some cases, the provider partner may collect information from you directly; in which cases the privacy policy of the provider partner may apply to the provider partner's use of your information. The privacy policy of our provider partners may differ from ours. If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of one of our provider partners, you should contact the provider partner directly for more information. Be aware that we may occasionally release information about visitors / members when release is appropriate to comply with law, to enforce our Terms of Service agreement, or to protect the rights, property or safety of users of the Site, the public, or the MYPOPKORN Site.

8\. Please also note that as our business grows, we may buy or sell various assets. In the unlikely event that we sell some or all of our assets, or our Site is acquired by another company, information about our visitors may be among the transferred assets.

 **WHEN MYPOPKORN DISCLOSES INFORMATION**

  * We provide personally identifiable information and non-personally-identifiable information to our subsidiaries, affiliate companies, or other businesses or people for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our privacy policy, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 
  * We do share non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third-parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the MYPOPKORN Site. 
  * We may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with any law or to respond to a court order or an order from any governing body or statutory authority.
  * MYPOPKORN also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information that MYPOPKORN believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of our web site, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of MYPOPKORN, our users / members or others. 

**INVITATIONS AND OTHER COMMUNICATIONS TO NON-MEMBERS**

MYPOPKORN members can invite friends to join the service by sending invitation emails via our automated invitation system. The MYPOPKORN Site stores the email addresses that members provide so that the respondents may be added to the friend's list of the member sending the invitations, and also to send reminders of the invitations. The MYPOPKORN Site does not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations, invitation reminders (up to three (3) per email address). Recipients of invitations from MYPOPKORN may contact the MYPOPKORN Site to request the removal of their information from our database.

MYPOPKORN members may also store email addresses of people they know in their internal MYPOPKORN address book and may also choose to send invitations and other communications to those addresses.

You may prevent email invitations from us by sending a single email with the subject "BLOCK" to unsubscribe@MYPOPKORN.com. Please note that the email must come from the account you wish to block.

 **OUR COMMITMENT TO CHILDRENS' PRIVACY**

The Site is NOT directed to or intended for people under the age of Sixteen. A User less than 16 (Sixteen) years of age should not register to use the Site. MYPOPKORN does not knowingly collect any personal information from people under the age of sixteen. If you are a parent of a child under the age of sixteen and you have questions about our Site or Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact the MYPOPKORN Privacy Coordinator at [privacy@MYPOPKORN.com](mailto:privacy@mypopkorn.com). Those between the age of Sixteen and Eighteen are to provide either of their parents Email ID and an Email will be send informing that their ward has registered himself/herself to use the MYPOPKORN.com services. The parent will be legally bound by any acts/deeds/Violation of MYPOPKORN.com Terms of Use & Privacy Policy by their wards. 

**OUR COMMITMENT TO DATA SECURITY**

We use commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to MYPOPKORN and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, MYPOPKORN makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

If MYPOPKORN learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. MYPOPKORN may post a notice on the MYPOPKORN Site if a security breach occurs. 

**SPECIAL NOTE TO INTERNATIONAL USERS / MEMBERS**

MYPOPKORN is hosted in India and is intended for and directed to users / members in India. If you are a user / member accessing the MYPOPKORN Site from any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, protection and disclosure, that differ from Indian laws, please be advised that through your use of the MYPOPKORN Site, this Privacy Notice, and our Terms of Use, you are transferring your personal information to India and you consent to that transfer. We will only be complying with the legal provisions on the subject matter as applicable in India from time to time.

 **HOW YOU CAN MAKE CHANGES TO YOUR INFORMATION**

**NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES**  
We reserve the right at any time to: change the terms of this Agreement; change the Services, including eliminating or modifying any content on or feature of the Site; or change/charge any fees or charges for use of the Services. Any changes we make will be effective immediately on notice, which we may give either by posting the new Agreement on the Site or via electronic mail. Your use of the Services after such notice will be deemed acceptance of such changes. Be sure to review this Agreement periodically to ensure your familiarity with the most current version. You will always be able to tell when the version was last updated by checking the "Last Revised" date in the header of this agreement. 

**CONFLICT RESOLUTION**  
We are committed to resolving disputes as soon as feasible and shall endeavor to resolve all disputes brought to our notice in keeping with the mechanism prescribed, within 15 working days of such receipt.

 **CONTACT INFORMATION**  
If site users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:  
E-mail: [customercare@mypopkorn.com](mailto:customercare@mypopkorn.com)  
Telephone: +91 22-4077 6767  
Postal Address: Madhu Industrial Estate, Ground Floor, P B Marg, Worli, Mumbai  
State: Maharashtra  
Pin code: 400013  
Country: India

**WEBSITE ADMINISTRATION**  
Business name: myPOPKORN.com Address: Madhu Industrial Estate, Ground Floor, P B Marg, Worli, Mumbai, State: Maharashtra Pin code: 400013 Country: India Website URL: [http://www.MYPOPKORN.com](http://www.mypopkorn.com/)
